amerisave.com 2018-12-24

# Privacy Policy - AmeriSave Mortgage Corporation

### Privacy Policy

You can download a copy of AmeriSave’s Privacy Policy

**Privacy**

At AmeriSave Mortgage Corporation (“AmeriSave”), we are dedicated to upholding a strict code of ethics and business practices. In doing so, we are committed to protecting the privacy and security of those who access and use our website (“Site”). This online privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) is in addition to any privacy notice or policy you may receive from AmeriSave before or after a customer relationship is established. This Privacy Policy pertains only to information collected through your use of this Site.

This Privacy Policy is designed to inform you about the types of information that we gather about you, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of that information.

**Collection and Use of Your Personal Information**

For all visitors to its Site, AmeriSave collects general data pertaining to each Site visitor, such as the visitor’s IP address, operating system, browser type and version number, and the web pages viewed. This information is aggregated with all other visitor information.

You may also provide financial information to us through this Site for the purpose of considering an extension of credit to you and extending credit to you. Thus, AmeriSave will receive through this Site personal information, which means information by which specific individuals can be identified, including by name, identification number, mailing address, e-mail address, and other personal characteristics or attributes, from those who provide it to AmeriSave through the Site.

All personal and financial information acquired by AmeriSave will be used fairly and lawfully; AmeriSave will not use such personal information for purposes that are incompatible with the purposes it was requested and received. For example, AmeriSave will use your personal information to respond to your questions; to help us to improve our website and your online experience; to provide you with information about our products and services; to transact business with you; and as otherwise allowed by law.

AmeriSave will not share personal information with third parties, with other divisions of AmeriSave, or with any affiliate of AmeriSave, except as follows:

AmeriSave partners with third parties to provide specific services required in the processing of your loan, to communicate with you on its behalf of AmeriSave, and to improve services provided by AmeriSave by seeking reviews from you. The information that is shared with these third parties is done so in order to acquire credit reports, appraisals, titles, to communicate with you, and to improve services by seeking reviews. We share names or other personally identifiable information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

Information Provided by You and Collected by AmeriSave, which may be shared with these third-party service providers, includes:

  * Client name, address, employment history, social security numbers, income, credit balances, property insurance coverage and other representations made by the client.
  * Client payment history, account balance, and other transactional information.
  * Information obtained from consumer credit-reporting agencies (including credit history and creditworthiness).

AmeriSave will only share information with third party service providers as required to close your loan. AmeriSave may also disclose information in response to subpoenas, governmental requests or other legal process, or to otherwise protect our legal or contractual obligations. AmeriSave will never rent, sell, or share any personal information to third party marketers.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a type of identifier sent from a website to your computer system via your web browser to provide tailored features. AmeriSave uses first-party cookies to track and analyze visitors’ usage of the Site. AmeriSave also uses first-party cookies to secure and confirm your information when logging into secure areas of the Site with your private login name and password.

The Site also contains content from third parties that may use “third-party” cookies for advertising purposes. The information shared with advertisers is anonymous and does not contain any personal or confidential data and cannot be used to identify individuals.

**Do Not Track**

AmeriSave tracks its customers over time, but not across third party web sites and not to provide targeted advertising, and therefore does not respond to Do Not Track (DNT) signals. However, some third party sites do keep track of your browsing activities when they serve you content, which enables them to tailor what they present to you. If you are visiting such sites, your web browser may allow you to set the DNT signal on your browser so that third parties (particularly advertisers) know you do not want to be tracked. Third parties cannot collect any personally identifiable information from AmeriSave’s website unless you provide it to them directly.

**Other Service Providers**

From time to time we may use third party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. Such advertising companies may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web site and your interaction with our ads. For instance, it may keep track of how many of our ads you had seen before visiting our site. This is primarily accomplished through ad-serving software, including cookies and Action Tags (commonly referred to as Web Beacons or GIF tags), which we place on various pages within our Site.

AmeriSave also contracts with third parties to communicate with you via mail, e-mail, text, and telephone calls on AmeriSave’s behalf in order to provide AmeriSave’s services, improve those services and to offer you the opportunity to provide a review of those services. AmeriSave obtains consent prior to sending any text messages sent to you.

AmeriSave’s contracted advertising companies may use information about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide ads about goods and services of interest to you.

We may use Criteo Email that finds visitors of Criteo advertising clients’ properties (websites, apps and newsletters) and sends them personalized emails. Criteo uses cookies to single out users and then personalize ads based on their browsing experience. To learn more or opt out of Criteo Email, please visit the Criteo Email website.

The AmeriSave Site also utilizes Google Analytics for Display Advertisers that is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of the Site, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Visitors can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertisers and opt out of customized Google Display Network ads by visiting Google’s Ads Settings.

**Security**

AmeriSave takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line. When our application form asks users to enter sensitive information, it is encrypted and is protected with state of the art encryption software – SSL (Secure Sockets Layer). While on a secure page, the lock icon on Web browsers becomes locked.

**Communication Preferences**

By submitting your name, email address and phone number anywhere on Amerisave.com you may receive phone calls and emails regarding your interest in AmeriSave. If AmeriSave receives your information through third party lead providers, you may receive phone and email correspondence regarding your interest in a mortgage. AmeriSave will contact you via email and phone during your loan process as needed to complete your loan. We may also contact you in the future to provide information regarding other financial or consumer products that we feel may interest you. You may opt-out of any correspondence which is not directly linked to your transaction by clicking on the unsubscribe or manage email subscriptions link in any non-transactional email. Customers may not opt-out of emails directly related to their transaction with AmeriSave.

**Our Contact Information**

AmeriSave Mortgage Corporation  
3525 Piedmont Rd NE  
8 Piedmont Center, Suite 600  
Atlanta, GA 30305

AmeriSave reserves the right to change its practices concerning information gathered from visitors to its websites. If such changes occur, this Privacy Policy will be updated. Visitors should check back periodically to confirm the then-current terms of this Policy. This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

Last Update: August 16, 2017
